Damanggi Pratama Aryansyah

Fresh Graduate - Bachelor of Economics (B.Econ.)

South Jakarta, Indonesia | 0895322573480 | <u>damanggipratama@gmail.com</u> | www.linkedin.com/in/damanggipratamaa | https://damanggipratamaa.github.io/cv-portfolio/

SUMMARY

I am an independent and self-motivated person who able to accomplish task with clarity and enthusiasm. I just got my bachelor's degree in economics and have 1+ year experience as a business owner. College life made me have a strong interest in data analysis, trade, economic research, policy review, and sustainability issues. I am also have passion in sports, particularly football.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Mandalika Grand Prix Association - Jakarta & Lombok, Indonesia

Administration and Document Controller (January 2022 - Present)

- Coordinate with the immigration related to the rules and regulations that apply in making VISA
- Welcoming and directing foreigners at the airport to follow the protocol flow that has been made by policy makers
- Communicate with Ikatan Motor Indonesia (IMI) to make purchases and prepare various needs for Marshall who is on duty in the race
- Collect and process 200+ data of foreigners for the issuance of VISA related to Moto GP events
- Carry out an inventory of 5000+ company assets in the Pertamina Mandalika International Street Circuit area

Appen - New South Wales, Australia

Data Collector (October 2021 - December 2021)

• Conduct research and surveys to collect various types of data needed for the development of Artificial Intelligence (AI)

Kole Kopi - Jakarta, Indonesia

Owner (April 2019 – September 2020)

- Create product packaging design and promotional media to be published via Instagram
- Make a recapitulation report contains total product sold per-week and feedback from customers
- Manage administrative activities with various parties for sponsorship cooperation

ORGANIZATIONAL AND COMMITTEE EXPERIENCE

Jazz Goes to Campus - Depok, Indonesia

Procurement Coordinator (February 2020 – February 2021)

- Interact with other divisions in Jazz Goes to Campus to follow-up the needs that we must provide in welcoming more than 20.000 visitors
- Lead weekly division meetings to ensure event needs related to technical, printing, and goods rented from vendors
- Negotiate and collect documents for administrative needs from more than 10 vendors who participate in open tender

Himpunan Pengusaha Muda Indonesia (HIPMI) PT Universitas Indonesia - Depok, Indonesia

Deputy General Treasurer for Social and Humanitarian Affairs (June 2019 – February 2021)

- Prepare budgeting of HIPMI's activities related to social and humanitarian affairs such as social services, donations to orphans, and distribution of aid funds for cadger in need)
- Present a budget realization report at the organization's general meeting

Islamic Business and Economics Community (IBEC) - Depok, Indonesia

Head of Internal Bureau (January 2019 – February 2020)

- Intenalize and protect sense of belonging between more than 60 IBEC functionaries through various activities such as self-development program, team building, half-year and end-year evaluation
- Deliver a report of bureau expenditures to IBEC's general treasurer for administrative activities and disbursement of block grants from the dean

Football Association of Economics Universitas Indonesia (FAE UI) - Depok, Indonesia

Chairman (February 2018 – January 2019)

- Arrange weekly training program and looking for competitions to participate in
- Coordinate with the sports department of BEM FEB UI concerning the sustainability and financial condition
- Attend technical meetings with organizer of the competitions being participated

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITAS INDONESIA (2017 - 2021)

Bachelor of Economics, Islamic Economics – 3.43/4.00

Thesis title: "The Influence of Worker's Religiosity on Labor Market Outcome in Indonesia: Analysis of IFLS 5"

ORGANIZATIONAL SKILLS

- Discussing and problem solving
- Friendly and professional communication

COMPUTER SKILLS

- STATA
- Adobe Photoshop
- Coreldraw
- Python
- Canva

MICROSOFT SKILLS

- Microsoft Excel (Pivot table, Vlookup, Count If)
- Microsoft Word
- Microsoft Powerpoint
- Microsoft Power BI

ADMINISTRATIVE SKILLS

- Collecting and compiling documents
- Perform data input
- Archive and financial arrangements